Mahitab Mohamed Musa Frontend Developer

- ™ mahitab 90@outlook.com
- +249119727672
- ♥ Khartoum, Sudan
- http://mahitabmohamed.com/
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mahitab-mohamed-014775135
- https://github.com/mahitab101

Profile

Seasoned and independent Front End Developer with 5 years of experience in blending the art of design with the skills of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development, proactive feature optimization, and relentless debugging. and very passionate about aesthetics, programming, and UI design.

Professional Experience

Senior Frontend Developer

Oasis Computer systems

□

06/2021 - present Khartoum,, Sudan

- Worked in an agile environment with weekly stand-ups.
- Determining the structure and design of the web
- Using the latest frontend technology for design and develop.
- · Producing, maintaining, and modifying websites and user interfaces.
- Develop and improve websites and web applications.
- · Fixing any website issues or bugs that arise

Web Developer 02/2019 - 11/2020 BHM & Partners 🛮

- designing and building Websites and web applications.
- Editing, writing, and designing Website content.
- Determining user needs by analyzing technical requirements.

Frontend Developer

Nubi-ict

03/2018 - 01/2020 Khartoum, ,Sudan

- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Developing features to enhance the user experience.
- Striking a balance between functional and aesthetic design.
- Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones.
- Building reusable code for future use.
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Utilizing a variety of markup languages to write web pages.

Frontend Developer Remote

devsharp ♂

- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Design mobile-based features.
- Building reusable code for future use.
- Design the interface for mobile apps.
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Creating tools that enhance the user's website experience.

Riyadh, , Saudi Arabia

Web Developer 04/2015 - 10/2017 Gadarif, ,Sudan

Gadarif University ♂

Main duties performed:

• Digital content manager, Full responsibility for university sites, design and develop websites, publish web content and keep it up to date

	Skills	s	
Frontend	• • • •	HTML5	• • • •
CSS	• • • • •	JavaScript	• • • • •
Bootstrap	• • • • •	Backend	• • • • •
Angular	• • • • •	React	• • • • •
JQuery	• • • • •	ASP.Net Core	• • • • •
Rest API	• • • • •	Entity Framework	• • • • •
.Net Core	• • • • •	Adobe Photoshop	• • • • •
Adobe Photoshop	• • • • •	Git on Github	• • • •
Azure	• • • • •	DevOps	• • • • •
Agile	• • • • •	Scrum	• • • • •

Projects

Concord Aggregator

CRM

Todo-List ☑

Manage your list item in one place

ECommerce

Admin Dashboard

	Education			
Master of Information Technology Al-Neelain University ☑		01/2015 – 10/2017 Khartoum, ,Sudan		
BS.c Gadarif University ☑		2009 – 2013 Gadarif, Sudan		
Languages				
Arabic	English			